[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the US Army Air Force B-29 bomber, that dropped the atomic bomb on Nagasaki, Japan on August 9, 1945?", "correct_answer": "Bocks Car", "incorrect_answers": ["Enola Gay", "General Belgrano", "Memphis Belle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All pigs are classified as un-Kosher meaning they can not be eaten by Jewish people.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which US state is the city of Truth or Consequences located?", "correct_answer": "New Mexico", "incorrect_answers": ["Mexico", "Utah", "Texas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie directed by Tim Burton was filmed completely in black-and-white?", "correct_answer": "Ed Wood", "incorrect_answers": ["Mars Attacks!", "Big Fish", "Frankenweenie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On January 24, 1984, the Macintosh personal computer was introduced to the world by Apple Inc. How did the Macintosh brand get its name?", "correct_answer": "It was named after an apple cultivar.", "incorrect_answers": ["The name was formed from the first letters of the Apple team members who invented it.", "They named it after its creators late grandfather.", "It was named after its creator."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A water bowl should be kept within easy access for your dog at all times.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sugar on snow is a popular New England treat. It is boiled maple syrup cooled in snow and placed on sticks. Which food item is not traditionally served with this candy?", "correct_answer": "Shortbread cookies", "incorrect_answers": ["Yeast risen Donuts", "Coffee", "Sour Dill Pickle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There are more ladles of broth to be added to risotto until the rice reaches the al dente state. You should add each ladle of broth when this happens.", "correct_answer": "The rice absorbs the previous one", "incorrect_answers": ["The rice absorbs the water", "The rice becomes hard", "The rice becomes soft"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three of the following US states have a motto consisting of one single word in English. Which one does not belong to the group?", "correct_answer": "West Virginia", "incorrect_answers": ["Utah", "Texas", "Rhode Island"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What river flows through the central part of the French capital, Paris?", "correct_answer": "Seine", "incorrect_answers": ["Loire", "Charente", "Rhine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why were the insects known as snakeflies given this interesting name?", "correct_answer": "Their body is elongated.", "incorrect_answers": ["They hiss.", "They have a venomous bite.", "They have snake skin color patterns on their back."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Only sea turtles do not care for their young.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]